(Amy:)I would. I love cats.
(Amy:)They're the epitome
of indifference.
(Sheldon:)Ah, then you may find
Zazzles a little cloying.
(Leonard:)I saw what you did there.
(Mrs Cooper:)He thinks he's such a smarty pants.
(Mrs Cooper:)He's no different from any man.
(Mrs Cooper:)You tell 'em not to do
something, that's all
(Mrs Cooper:)they want to do.
(Mrs Cooper:)If I hadn't told my brother Stumpy
(Mrs Cooper:)not to clear out the
wood chipper by hand,
(Mrs Cooper:)we'd still be calling him Edward.
(Mrs Cooper:)Now, don't you move.
(Mrs Cooper:)I'll bring over all the food.
(Leonard:)No, no, no, I can do it.
(Mrs Cooper:)Well, isn't that sweet?
(Sheldon:)Thank you, Amy.
(Sheldon:)Here's your cat.
(Sheldon:)And here's your $20.
AMY: Next!
(Sheldon:)Thank you, Amy.
(Sheldon:)Here's your cat.
(Sheldon:)And here's your $20.
AMY: Next!